Guide to the Lucy Monroe Calhoun Family Photographs and Papers, 1886-1993 and undated, bulk 1911-1933 RL.11103
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Developing out paper and gelatin silver photographs, 1900-1941 and undated; 1
  - Beijing, 1910-1941; 2
    - Manchu woman, seated beside flowering plant, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-173)
      满族妇女坐着，旁边是开花的盆栽
    - Chinese New Year celebration, 1941, 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-174)
      1941年庆祝农历新年，合影
      China New Year 1941
    - Children at Chinese New Year celebration, 1941, 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-175)
      1941年庆祝农历新年，孩子们合影
    - Street scene, with Westerners at center, 1910s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-176)
      大街上，中间有几个外国人
    - Courtyard at home of Colonel and Mrs. Isaac Newell, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-177)
      艾萨克·纽厄尔夫妇家的院子
      The Tranquil Abode of the Humble Heart. With Best Wishes for Christmas and the New Year. Colonel and Mrs. Isaac Newell. A court yard of the Tranquil abode.
    - Street musician, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-178)
      街头艺人
    - The candy man, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-179.1)
      卖冰糖葫芦的小贩
      The candy man
    - The candy man, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-179.2)
      Version of RL11103-P-179.1.
    - Funeral procession, 1920s; 5.5 x 3.25 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-180)
      送葬队伍
    - Funeral procession with Chinese man, center, walking away from camera, 1920s; 5.5 x 3.25 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-181)
      送葬队伍，中间一男子回看镜头
    - Funeral procession with man on white horse, center, 1920s; 5.5 x 3.25 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-182)
      送葬队伍，中间一人骑白马
    - Funeral procession, with musicians and flag bearer, 1920s; 5.5 x 3.25 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-183)
      送葬队伍，有奏乐者和执幡者
      Funeral -- China
    - Funeral procession with banners, 1920s; 5.5 x 3.25 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-184)
      送葬队伍，执幡者
      Funeral procession
    - The catafalque behind a crowd, 1920s; 5.5 x 3.25 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-185)
      送葬队伍，人群后的灵柩
    - The catafalque, 1920s; 5.5 x 3.25 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-186)
      灵柩
      The catafalque
    - The widow in the funeral procession, 1920s; 5.5 x 3.25 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-187)
      送葬队伍中坐在车里的寡妇
      The widow in the funeral procession
    - Paper models for funeral procession, 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-188)
      送葬队伍中的纸扎人
    - Street scene near the Camel Gate--between Tartar and Chinese Walls, 1920s; 5.5 x 3.25 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-189)
      广安门附近的街市
      Near the Camel Gate--between Tartar and Chinese Walls
    - Street children?, 1920s; 5.5 x 3.25 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-190)
      大街上孩童们合影
      Street children?
    - Manchu women and children, 1920s; 5.5 x 3.25 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-191.1)
      满人妇女和儿童
      Manchu and Chinese (Manchu head-dress is the large flat one.)
    - Manchu women and children, 1920s; 5.5 x 3.25 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-191.2)
      Copy of RL11103-P-191.1.
    - A baby girl, 1920s; 2 x 3.25 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-192)
      小女童
      A girl baby. This
    - Brothers pose in front of wall, 1920s; 3 x 3.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-193)
      兄弟俩站在墙根
      Brothers
    - Group at the races, 1920s; 3.75 x 3 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-194)
      栏杆后看赛马的人群
      Group at the races
    - Kindergarten pupils at luncheon, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-195)
      孩子们准备吃午饭
      Kindergarten pupils at luncheon. Return photo to Miss Harriet Monroe, 1720 Railway Exchange, Chicago, Ill
    - Kindergarten pupils in Peking, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-196)
      北京的孩童们
      High class kindergarten pupils in Peking. Return photo to Miss Harriet Monroe, 1720 Railway Exchange, Chicago, Ill
    - Kindergarten pupils, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-197)
    - Street scene with six children, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-198)
      六个孩子站在街上
    - Packing for travel, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-199)
      准备启程
    - Outdoor merchant, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-200)
      街边摊贩
    - Indoor merchant, left of room, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-201)
      古玩店，店铺的左面
    - Indoor merchant, right of room, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-202)
      古玩店，店铺的右面
    - Street vendor, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-203)
      街边小贩
    - Street scene with young boy, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-204)
      男孩站在街上
    - Food vendors, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-205)
      卖小吃的贩子
    - Street scene with several merchants, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-206)
      街边的几个摊贩
    - Street merchant with sign for Chinese medicine, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-207)
      街边的中药摊贩
    - Transporting millstones, 1920s; 5.5 x 3.25 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-208)
      运石碾子
      Transporting mill-stones
    - Roadside Restaurant, 1920s; 5.5 x 3.25 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-209)
      路边卖饭的摊子
      Baker at work?
    - Paifang & Street, 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-210)
      大街上的牌坊
    - Race course pagoda, 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-211.1)
      赛马场附近的塔
      Peking Race Course Pagoda
    - Race course pagoda, 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-211.2)
      Version of RL11103-P-211.1. Photograph has black border.
    - The Chien-Men (Qianmen) temple tower from top of Tartar Wall, 1920s; 3.25 x 5.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-212)
      内城的前门（正阳门）城墙上的门楼
      The Chien-Men temple tower from top of Tartar Wall. Illus. 3 1/2?
    - The Chien-Men gate (Qianmen), 1920s; 3.25 x 5.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-213)
      前门（正阳门）
      The Chien-Men
    - Chien-Men gate (Qianmen), 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-214)
      Chien Men Gate. I see it from my window, and I lack color
    - Chi Hua Men (Qihuamen), 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-215)
      朝阳门（齐化门）
      Chi Hua Men
    - On the city wall, one of the gates, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-216)
      一处城门上
      On the city wall, one of the gates
    - Tien An Men (Tiananmen), 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-217)
      天安门
      Tien an Men
    - Wu Men from within Forbidden City, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-218.1)
      紫禁城内看午门
      Wu Men from within Forbidden City
    - Wu Men from within Forbidden City, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-218.2)
      Version of RL11103-P-218.1. Photograph has black border.
    - Lucy Calhoun in a rickshaw at the station, 1920s; 5.5 x 3.25 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-219.1)
      露西·嘉乐恒坐着人力车在车站
      Aunt Lucy at the station as we said farewell
    - Lucy Calhoun in a rickshaw at the station, 1920s; 5.5 x 3.25 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-219.2)
      Version of RL11103-P-219.1.
    - Polly Root Collier in a camel train, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-220)
      外国女士骑着骆驼排成一队，波莉·鲁特·科利尔是其中之一。
    - Polly Root Collier, fourth in a camel train, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-221)
      骆驼队，波莉·鲁特·科利尔是第四个骑者
    - Riding coal camels, Etelka, Eliz. Belts, ?, Polly Root Collier, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-222)
      通常运煤的骆驼队，骑骆驼的有伊特卡、伊利兹、贝尔和波莉·鲁特·科利尔
      Riding coal camels, Etelka, Eliz. Belts, ?, PRC
    - Camel train with Polly Root Collier (2nd from left) turns a corner, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-223)
      骆驼队转弯，波莉·鲁特·科利尔是左边第二个骑者
    - Polly Root Collier (front) in China, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-224)
      波莉·鲁特·科利尔（前面）坐在骆驼上
      Polly Root Collier (front) in China
    - Camels under the Tartar Wall, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-225)
      内城墙边的骆驼队
      Camels under the Tartar Wall
    - Through the Camel Gate, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-226)
      骆驼队入城门（阜城门）
      Through the Camel Gate
    - Corner of Tartar Wall--Peking, 1920s; 3.25 x 5.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-227)
      北京内城一角
      Corner of Tartar Wall--Peking
    - Outside the Tartar Wall, 1920s; 5.5 x 3.25 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-228)
      内城墙外，驼队
      Outside the Tartar Wall of Peking
    - Camel train outside of Tartar Wall, 1920s; 5.5 x 3.25 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-229)
      Outside the Tartar Wall
    - Beyond the Camel Gate, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-230)
      阜城门外
      Beyond the Camel Gate
    - Beginning of camel train beyond the Camel Gate, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-231)
      阜城门外，驼队
    - Long camel train beyond the Camel Gate, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 11, Print RL11103-P-232)
      阜城门外，长长的驼队
    - Entrance to the Temple of Heaven, 1920s; 4x 2.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 12, Print RL11103-P-233)
      天坛门
    - Circular Mound Altar at the Temple of Heaven, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 12, Print RL11103-P-234)
      天坛的圜丘坛
      The Temple of Heaven Altar at the Centre of the Earth
    - Pailou of the Circular Mound Altar, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 12, Print RL11103-P-235)
      圜丘坛的牌楼
      P'ai Lou and part of the Temple of Heaven
    - Approach to the Circular Mound Altar, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 12, Print RL11103-P-236)
      圜丘坛的台阶
    - On a level of the Circular Mound Altar, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 12, Print RL11103-P-237)
      圜丘坛的一层
    - Circular Mound Altar, detail, 1920s; 5.5 x 3 in. (Box 1, Folder 12, Print RL11103-P-238)
      圜丘坛局部近景
      Temple of Heaven-- detail
    - Stairs of Circular Mound Altar, detail, 1920s; 4.75 x 6.75 in. (Box 1, Folder 12, Print RL11103-P-239)
    - Hall of Prayer for Good Harvests, 1920s; 3 x 5.5 in. (Box 1, Folder 12, Print RL11103-P-240)
      祈年殿
      Temple of Night? Temple of Heaven
    - Approach to Hall of Prayer for Good Harvests, 1920s; 5.5 x 3 in. (Box 1, Folder 12, Print RL11103-P-241)
    - Pailou at the Imerpial College, 1920s; 6.75 x 4.75 in. (Box 2, Folder 9, Print RL11103-P-243)
      国子监的"圜槁教泽"牌楼
      Pailou at the Confucian Temple
    - Temple of Confucius. Way of Sacrifice Hall, 1920s; 5.25 x 3.25 in. (Box 1, Folder 7, Print RL11103-P-244)
      孔庙，通向大成殿
      Temple of Confucius. Way of Sacrifice Hall. Stamp of Mei Li Photographic Studio, Peiping
    - Hall of Classics at the Imerpial College, 1920s; 5.25 x 3.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 9, Print RL11103-P-245)
      国子监的辟雍大殿
      Hall of Classics. Temple of Confucius
    - Temple of Confucius. The Gate, 1920s; 5.25 x 3.25 in. (Box 1, Folder 7, Print RL11103-P-246)
      孔庙 ，大成门
      Temple of Confucius. The Gate. Stamp of Mei Li Photographic Studio, Peiping
    - Temple of Confucius. Sacrifice Hall, 1920s; 3.25 x 5.25 in. (Box 1, Folder 7, Print RL11103-P-247)
      孔庙 ，大成殿
      Temple of Confucius. Sacrifice Hall. Stamp of Mei Li Photographic Sudio, Peiping
    - Temple of Confucius. Marble dragon step, 1920s; 3.25 x 5.25 in. (Box 1, Folder 7, Print RL11103-P-248)
      孔庙 ，大殿前台阶上的龙形石刻
      Temple of Confucius. Marble dragon step. Stamp of Mei Li Photographic Studio, Peiping
    - Temple of Confucius. The cedar, 1920s; 3.25 x 5.25 in. (Box 1, Folder 7, Print RL11103-P-249)
      孔庙，香柏树
      Temple of Confucius. The ceder [sic] Stamp of Mei Li Photographic Studio, Peiping
    - Temple of Confucius. Monument Tower, 1920s; 3.25 x 5.25 in. (Box 1, Folder 7, Print RL11103-P-250)
      孔庙 ，御碑亭
      Temple of Confucius. Monument Tower. Stamp of Mei Li Photographic Studio, Peiping
    - Temple of Confucius. Sacrifice Hall roof corner, 1920s; 3.25 x 5.25 in. (Box 1, Folder 7, Print RL11103-P-251)
      Temple of Confucius. Sacrifice Hall roof corner. Stamp of Mei Li Photographic Studio, Peiping
    - Temple of Confucius. Desciple's Shrines, 1920s; 5.25 x 3.25 in. (Box 1, Folder 7, Print RL11103-P-252)
      孔庙，弟子的配享牌位
      Temple of Confucius. Desciple's Shrines. Stamp of Mei Li Photographic Studio, Peiping
    - Temple of Confucius. Desciple's Tablets, 1920s; 5.25 x 3.25 in. (Box 1, Folder 7, Print RL11103-P-253)
      Temple of Confucius. Desciple's Tablets. Stamp of Mei Li Photographic Studio, Peiping
    - Temple of Confucius. Confucius' Tablet, 1920s; 3.25 x 5.25 in. (Box 1, Folder 7, Print RL11103-P-254)
      孔庙，孔子神牌位
      Temple of Confucius. Confucius' Tablet. Stamp of Mei Li Photographic Studio, Peiping
    - Temple of Confucius. New stone drums. 200 years old, 1920s; 3.25 x 5.25 in. (Box 1, Folder 7, Print RL11103-P-255)
      孔庙，两百年历史的新石鼓
      Temple of Confucius. New stone drums. 200 years old. Stamp of Mei Li Photographic Studio, Peiping
    - Temple of Confucius. Old stone drums. 2700 years old., 1920s; 5.25 x 3.25 in. (Box 1, Folder 7, Print RL11103-P-256)
      孔庙，两千七百年历史的旧石鼓
      Temple of Confucius. Old stone drums. 2700 years old. Stamp of Mei Li Photographic Studio, Peiping
  - Outside Beijing, 1900-1939; 3
    - Qufu. Tomb of Confucius, 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in (Box 2, Folder 1, Print RL11103-P-242)
      曲阜，孔林，孔子墓
      Chufu. Tomb of Confucius
    - The Great Wall of China, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-257)
      长城
      The Great Wall
    - The Great Wall of China, hand-tinted photograph, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-258)
      长城，手工上色
    - The Great Wall of China, photographed from an airplane, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-259)
      飞机上俯瞰长城
    - Portion of the Great Wall of China, photographed from an airplane, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-260)
    - Camel Boy at Great Wall of China, 1920s; 5 x 3 in. (Box 2, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-261)
      长城脚下骆驼脚夫
      Camel Boy at Great Wall
    - Rising segment of the Great Wall of China, 1920s; 5 x 3 in. (Box 2, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-262)
      越来越高的一段长城
      Great Wall of China
    - Highest Point of Great Wall of China, 1920s; 5 x 3 in. (Box 2, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-263)
      长城的最高点
      Highest Point of Great Wall
    - Stepped slope of Great Wall of China, 1920s; 5 x 3 in. (Box 2, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-264)
      长城上的一段台阶
      Steppet Slope of Great Wall
    - Great Wall of China looking through Gateway, 1920s; 3 x 5 in. (Box 2, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-265)
      透过城楼拱门看长城
      Great Wall looking through Gate way
    - Battlement from Gateway, 1920s; 3 x 5 in. (Box 2, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-266)
      从拱门看长城垛口
      Battlement from Gate way
    - A part of Great Wall of China that features double walls, 1920s; 5 x 3 in. (Box 2, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-267)
      长城有两条城墙的一段
      A Part of Double Walls
    - Sedan Chair at Great Wall of China, 1920s; 5 x 3 in. (Box 2, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-268)
      长城脚下四人抬轿
      Sedan Chair at Great Wall
    - Curving of Great Wall of China, 1920s; 5 x 3 in. (Box 2, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-269)
      曲折的长城
      Round Curving of Great Wall
    - Nankow (Nankou) Pass Wall, 1920s; 5 x 3 in. (Box 2, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-270)
      南口关处的长城
      Nankow Pass Wall
    - Close up of battlements at Great Wall of China, 1920s; 5 x 3 in. (Box 2, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-271)
      城墙垛口
    - Detail of Great Wall of China, 1920s; 5 x 3 in. (Box 2, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-272)
      长城的一段
    - Great Wall of China climbing hillside, 1920s; 5 x 3 in. (Box 2, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-273)
      顺山势越来越高的一段长城
    - Three men visiting Great Wall of China, 1920s; 5 x 3 in. (Box 2, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-274)
      三人在长城上
    - Pass in the Great Wall of China, 1920s; 3 x 5 in. (Box 2, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-275)
      长城上的一个关口
      Pass in the Great Wall
    - Great Wall of China climbing into distance, 1920s; 4.5 x 3.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 2, Print RL11103-P-276)
      Best Wishes for a Merry Xmas. M. S. Reeves
    - En route to Jehol (Rehe), 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 3, Print RL11103-P-277)
      前往热河（承德）途中
      En route to Jéhō
    - To Jehol (Rehe). Ku Pei Koa (Gubeikou) pass, (a temple), 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 3, Print RL11103-P-278)
      前往热河（承德）途中，古北口, 一个庙宇
      To Jehol. Ku Pei Koa pass
    - Jehol (Rehe), (Yongyou Temple pagoda), 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 3, Print RL11103-P-279)
      承德，永佑寺舍利塔
      Jehol
    - Jehol (Rehe) Potala Entrance, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 3, Print RL11103-P-280)
      承德，普陀宗乘之庙入口
      Jehol Potala Entrance
    - Jehol (Rehe) Potala, side view, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 3, Print RL11103-P-281.1)
      承德，普陀宗乘之庙侧面
    - Jehol (Rehe) Potala, side view, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 3, Print RL11103-P-281.2)
      Jehol Potala
      Copy of RL11103-P-281.1. Photograph has black border.
    - Jehol (Rehe) interior court, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 3, Print RL11103-P-282)
      承德，普陀宗乘之庙内部
    - Jehol (Rehe) (pavilion & trees by) water, 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 3, Print RL11103-P-283)
      承德，水边亭子和树木
    - Xiantong Temple pagodas, Wutai Mountian, 1930s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 15, Print RL11103-P-284.1)
      五台山显通寺佛塔
      Original caption incorrectly indicated location as Jehol. Photograph has black border.
    - Xiantong Temple pagodas, Wutai Mountians, 1930s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 15, Print RL11103-P-284.2)
      Lucy Calhoun
      Original caption incorrectly indicated location as Jehol.
    - Ming Tombs cedar, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 4, Print RL11103-P-285.1)
      明陵，松树
      Peking. Ming Tombs
    - Ming Tombs cedar, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 4, Print RL11103-P-285.2)
      Ming Tombs
      Copy of RL11103-P-285.1. Photograph has black border.
    - Pailou and Gate Tower at Chang Ling, Ming Tombs, 1920s; 3 x 5.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 4, Print RL11103-P-286.1)
      明长陵的棂星门和明楼
    - Pailou and Gate Tower at Chang Ling, Ming Tombs, 1920s; 3 x 5.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 4, Print RL11103-P-286.2)
      Version of RL11103-P-286.1.
    - Pedastal of column (of the stone archway) before procession of animals at Ming Tombs, 1920s; 5.25 x 3 in. (Box 2, Folder 4, Print RL11103-P-287)
      明十三陵石牌坊基座上雕刻的龙
      Pedastal of column before procession of animals at Ming Tombs
    - Gate Tower at Ming Tombs, 1920s; 3 x 5.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 4, Print RL11103-P-288)
      明十三陵的方城明楼
      The Great Ming Tomb
    - Animals at the Ming Tombs, 1920s; 5.25 x 3 in. (Box 2, Folder 4, Print RL11103-P-289)
      明十三陵神道两旁的石兽
      Animals at the Ming Tombs
    - Procession of animals at Ming Tombs, 1920s; 5.25 x 3 in. (Box 2, Folder 4, Print RL11103-P-290)
      Procession of animals -- Ming Tombs
    - Visitors and procession of animals at Ming Tombs, 1920s; 5.25 x 3 in. (Box 2, Folder 4, Print RL11103-P-291)
      明十三陵神道两旁的石兽及游人
    - One of the two warriors guarding entrance to the Ming Tombs, 1920s; 3 x 5.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 4, Print RL11103-P-292)
      明十三陵神道旁的石将军
      One of the 2 warriors guarding entrance to Ming Tombs
    - Ming Tombs--pavilion and winged columns, 1920s; 5.25 x 3 in. (Box 2, Folder 4, Print RL11103-P-293)
      明十三陵的神功圣德碑亭和华表
      Ming Tombs--pavilion and winged columns
    - Sedan chairs to the Ming Tombs, 1920s; 5.25 x 3 in. (Box 2, Folder 4, Print RL11103-P-294)
      坐轿子游览明十三陵
      Chairs to the Ming Tombs
    - The little temple at Pei Tai Ho (Beidaihe), 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 5, Print RL11103-P-295)
      北戴河的一个小庙
      The little temple at Pei Tai Ho
    - William J. Calhoun at Wuchang, 1910s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 5, Print RL11103-P-296)
      威廉·嘉乐恒坐在轿中，武昌
      At Wuchang, April 14, Uncle Calhoun
    - From the train window on the way to Peking, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 5, Print RL11103-P-297)
      坐火车途中从车窗拍摄
      From the train window on the way to Peking
    - Oxen plowing, 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 5, Print RL11103-P-298)
      牛拉犁耕田
      Oxen ploughing
    - Threshing field, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 5, Print RL11103-P-299)
      打谷场
      Threshing field
    - The harvest fields from a plane, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 5, Print RL11103-P-300)
      从飞机俯瞰丰收的农田
      The harvest fields
    - War in China--sleeping camels, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 5, Print RL11103-P-301)
      参与内战的军队，卧着休憩的骆驼
      War in China--sleeping camels
    - South China roofs, 1920s; 3x 5.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 5, Print RL11103-P-302)
      中国南方，俯瞰建筑屋顶
      South China roofs
    - Two men with rickshaw in front of stone Paifang, 1920s; 5.5 x 3.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 5, Print RL11103-P-502)
      石牌坊前的两人和黄包车
    - Pillar, silver pines, wall, and gate， Qing Tombs, 1920s; 5.5 x 3.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 5, Print RL11103-P-503)
      道旁石柱和隆恩门，清陵
    - Gate Tower, Qing Tombs, 1920s; 5.5 x 3.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 5, Print RL11103-P-504)
      清陵，隆恩城楼上
    - Qingliangzhencui Pai Fang gate and building, Wutai Mountains, 1930s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 15, Print RL11103-P-303)
      五台山碧山寺"清凉震萃"牌坊及后面的大殿
    - Qingliang shenjing Pai Fang gate, 1930s; 4.5 x 6.5 in (Box 2, Folder 15, Print RL11103-P-304)
      五台山塔院寺"清凉胜境"牌坊
    - Bronze pagoda at Xiantong Temple, 1930s; 4.5 x 6.5 in (Box 2, Folder 15, Print RL11103-P-305)
      五台山显通寺铜塔
    - People at Xiantong Temple, 1930s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 15, Print RL11103-P-306)
      五台山显通寺大殿前的五人
    - Graveyard at Mukden (Shenyang), 1920s; 5.25 x 3 in. (Box 2, Folder 5, Print RL11103-P-307)
      沈阳 陵墓
      Graveyard at Mukden
    - Mukden (Shenyang) Zhao Mausoleum (Zhaoling), 1920s; 3 x 5.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 5, Print RL11103-P-308)
      沈阳清昭陵
      Mukden?
    - Mukden (Shenyang) consulate?, 1920s; 5.25 x 3 in. (Box 2, Folder 5, Print RL11103-P-309)
      沈阳使馆？
      Mukden consulate?
    - Mukden (Shenyang) Zhao Mausoleum (Zhaoling), 1920s; 5.25 x 3 in. (Box 2, Folder 5, Print RL11103-P-310)
      Mukden tombs?
    - Tower of Buddhist Incense, from below, 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 6, Print RL11103-P-311)
      颐和园万寿山上的佛香阁
      Summer Palace
    - Summer Palace--Lotus on Lake, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 6, Print RL11103-P-312)
      颐和园昆明湖上荷叶荷花，远处的佛香阁
      Summer Palace--Lotus on Lake
    - Camel-back bridge, at distance, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 6, Print RL11103-P-313)
      颐和园昆明湖上的玉带桥（罗锅桥）
    - Canal through Camel-back bridge, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 6, Print RL11103-P-314)
    - Camel-back bridge & barge in which we were poled through the lotus leaves & rushes, 1920s; 5 x 3.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 6, Print RL11103-P-315)
      颐和园昆明湖上的玉带桥（罗锅桥），湖面上的荷叶和芦苇
      Camel back bridge & barge in which we were poled through the lotus leaves & rushes Lo Kuo Ch'iao
    - Camel-back bridge, with no plantings, 1920s; 5.25 x 3.25 in. (Box 2, Folder 6, Print RL11103-P-316)
      Camel back bridge-- Summer Palace
    - Camel-back bridge, side view, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 6, Print RL11103-P-317)
    - Summer Palace. Porcelain Pagoda, detail, 1920s; 4.5 x 6.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 6, Print RL11103-P-318)
      颐和园万寿山上的五彩琉璃多宝塔
      Summer Palace. Porcelain Pagoda
    - Porcelain Pagoda, 1920s; 3.25 x 5 in. (Box 2, Folder 6, Print RL11103-P-319)
      T'a
    - Near the Summer Palace, belonged to Prince Chun, 1920s; 6.5 x 4.5 in. (Box 2, Folder 6, Print RL11103-P-320)
      颐和园附近醇亲王的园子